{
    "subject": "resource/\u00d6stersunds_BS",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundingYear",
    "object": "1974",
    "human_readable": "\u00d6stersunds BS was founded in 1974.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.934162437915802,
            "question": "When was \u00d6stersunds BS founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8670462369918823,
            "question": "What is the founding year of \u00d6stersunds BS?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.75823974609375,
            "question": "Was \u00d6stersunds BS founded in the 20th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.731965959072113,
            "question": "In what decade was \u00d6stersunds BS established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.611407995223999,
            "question": "What year did \u00d6stersunds BS begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4855319857597351,
            "question": "Is \u00d6stersunds BS a relatively new organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48068714141845703,
            "question": "What type of organization is \u00d6stersunds BS?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4298645555973053,
            "question": "How long has \u00d6stersunds BS existed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40503519773483276,
            "question": "Has \u00d6stersunds BS been around for over 50 years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3724554479122162,
            "question": "Is \u00d6stersunds BS a recent addition to the sporting world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=\u00d6stersunds BS was founded in 1974.",
            "html": "dbpedia_79_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has \u00d6stersunds BS been around for over 50 years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_79_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How long has \u00d6stersunds BS existed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_79_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of organization is \u00d6stersunds BS?",
            "html": "dbpedia_79_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_79_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents support the statement that \u00d6stersunds BS was founded in 1974. The document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_79/re-ranker-msmarco/98.txt mentions \"\u00d6stersunds BS is a bandy club in \u00d6stersund, Sweden, established on 5 September 1974...\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state, \"\u00d6stersunds BS is a bandy club in \u00d6stersund, Sweden, established on 5 September 1974 when Ope IF's bandy section was disestablished.\" This supports the statement that \u00d6stersunds BS was founded in 1974."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}